Farrel Company Records 1989.0053
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Administrative Files, undated, 1844-1982
  - Subseries C: Master Agreement Files
    - Instruction - leases, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 146)
    - Legal - breach of contract/warranty, 1959 (Box 4:, Folder 147)
    - Legal - corporate reorganization, 1960 (Box 4:, Folder 148)
    - Legal aspects of antitrust laws, 1957 (Box 4:, Folder 149)
    - Legal opinions, 1940-1952 (Box 4:, Folder 150-151)
    - Patents - procedures for obtaining, 1958 (Box 4:, Folder 152)
    - Patents - in force, 1952-1953 (Box 4:, Folder 153)
    - Policy-contracts, 1958 (Box 4:, Folder 154)
    - Policy and procedure, 1956-1959 (Box 4:, Folder 155)
    - Procedure memo by J. LeMay, 1956 (Box 4:, Folder 156)
    - Roll prices, 1893-1894 (Box 4:, Folder 157)
    - Sales agreements (Box 4:, Folder 158)
    - Specimen copies - agreements (Box 4:, Folder 159)
    - Specimen letter - purchase and sale assets, 1955 (Box 4:, Folder 160)
    - Unsolicited ideas, 1958 (Box 4:, Folder 161)
    - Watson-Stillman Press Division, 1939 (Box 4:, Folder 162-163)
  - Subseries D: Minutes
    - Directors' meetings, 1958-1968 (Box 4:, Folder 164-165)
    - Disability committee, 1913 January - 1921 July (Box 4:, Folder 166)
    - Disability committee, 1910 April - 1912 December (Box 4:, Folder 167)
    - Executive Board, 1913 February - 1913 December (Box 4:, Folder 168)
    - Executive Board, 1914 January - 1914 June (Box 4:, Folder 169)
    - Executive Board, 1914 July - 1914 December (Box 4:, Folder 170)
    - Executive Board, 1915 January - 1915 December (Box 4:, Folder 171)
    - Executive Board, 1916 January - 1917 August (Box 4:, Folder 172)
    - Special meeting on corporate activity, 1968 (Box 4:, Folder 173-174)
  - Subseries E: Notebooks
    - Unidentified, 1905-1926 (Box 4:, Folder 175)
    - Accounts [Millor?] and Farrel, 1879 (Box 4:, Folder 176)
    - S.M. Blake - record of F. Farrel's expenses, 1868 (Box 4:, Folder 177)
    - David Bowen, 1886-1888 (Box 4:, Folder 178)
    - David Bowen, 1887-1888 (Box 4:, Folder 179)
    - David Bowen, 1890 (Box 4:, Folder 180)
    - David Bowen, 1897 (Box 4:, Folder 181)
    - David Bowen, 1897-1900 (Box 4:, Folder 182)
    - David Bowen, 1905 (Box 5:, Folder 183)
    - David Bowen, 1905 (Box 5:, Folder 184)
    - L.D. Chirgwin, 1922-1923 (Box 5:, Folder 185)
    - Diary, 1870 (Box 5:, Folder 186)
    - Diary, 1879 (Box 5:, Folder 187)
    - Almon Farrel, 1844 (Box 5:, Folder 188)
    - Almon Farrel's foundry account book, 1847 (Box 5:, Folder 189)
    - Franklin Farrel, Ansonia, 1849 (Box 5:, Folder 190)
    - Franklin Farrel, petty cash, 1852 (Box 5:, Folder 191)
    - Franklin Farrel, Ansonia, 1854 (Box 5:, Folder 192)
    - Franklin Farrel, memorandum, 1862 (Box 5:, Folder 193)
    - Franklin Farrel, 1868 (Box 5:, Folder 194)
    - Franklin Farrel, 1884 (Box 5:, Folder 195)
    - Franklin Farrel, safe deposit box, 1884 (Box 5:, Folder 196)
    - Franklin Farrel, 1888, 1889 (Box 5:, Folder 197)
    - Franklin Farrel, 1891 (Box 5:, Folder 198)
    - [Franklin Farrel?], 1892 (Box 5:, Folder 199)
    - Franklin Farrel, 1893 (Box 5:, Folder 200)
    - Franklin Farrel, jobs, 1896 (Box 5:, Folder 201)
    - Franklin Farrel, date book, 1898 (Box 5:, Folder 202)
    - Franklin Farrel, 1898 (Box 5:, Folder 203)
    - Franklin Farrel, Ansonia, 1899 (Box 5:, Folder 204)
    - Franklin Farrel, order 4497, 1901 (Box 5:, Folder 205)
    - [Franklin Farrel?], 1901 (Box 5:, Folder 206)
    - Franklin Farrel, 1910, 1906 (Box 5:, Folder 207)
    - Franklin Farrel, 3rd, 1934-1940 (Box 5:, Folder 208)
    - Farrel Johnson and Co., 1850 (Box 6:, Folder 209)
    - Franklin Hoadley, 1912-1924 (Box 6:, Folder 210)
    - Franklin Hoadley, 1915-1925 (Box 6:, Folder 211)
    - S.L. Marsden, 1869 (Box 6:, Folder 212)
    - Memorandum, 1849-1850 (Box 6:, Folder 213)
    - [G.W. Osborn?], 1908-1923 (Box 6:, Folder 214)
    - Pocket wedget, 1850 (Box 6:, Folder 215)
  - Subseries F: Personnel, undated
    - Company organization chart, 1962 (Box 6:, Folder 216)
    - Cost/wage rate manual, 1918 (Box 6:, Folder 217)
    - Departmental history, undated (Box 6:, Folder 218)
    - Employee account of duties, 1926 (Box 6:, Folder 219)
    - Employee citizenship and nationality statistics, 1918-1930 (Box 6:, Folder 220)
    - Employee interview, [1860s?] (Box 6:, Folder 221)
    - Employee introduction manual (Box 6:, Folder 222)
    - Employee obituary resolutions, 1951-1967 (Box 6:, Folder 223)
    - Employment statistics, 1932-1971 (Box 6:, Folder 224)
    - Employment statistics - Buffalo, 1942-1962 (Box 6:, Folder 225)
    - Labor agreement, 1979-1982 (Box 6:, Folder 226)
    - Labor relations scrapbook, 1916-1922 (Box 6:, Folder 227)
    - Learner training manual (Box 6:, Folder 228-229)
    - Payroll investment program, 1966-1968 (Box 6:, Folder 230)
    - Promotions/Appointments, 1967 (Box 6:, Folder 231)
    - Retirement pension plan, 1953-1955 (Box 6:, Folder 232)
    - Salary/wage rates, 1920-1922, 1972 (Box 6:, Folder 233)
    - Technical advisor rate book, 1969 (Box 6:, Folder 234)
    - Wage rates in England and U.S., 1950-1972 (Box 6:, Folder 235)
    - Wage statistics, 1906-1910 (Box 6:, Folder 236)
  - Subseries G: Reports and Surveys
    - Brady study, export division, 1954 (Box 6:, Folder 237)
    - Development and research report, 1943 (Box 6:, Folder 238)
    - Development of burden charges, 1935 (Box 6:, Folder 239-243)
    - General summaries, 1904 (Box 7:, Folder 244-245)
    - Index of Nielson survey, 1929 (Box 7:, Folder 246-249)
    - MacDonald Bros., Inc. - Buffalo plant, 1936 (Box 7:, Folder 250-250)
    - McKinsey and Co. - reorganization plan, 1943 (Box 7:, Folder 252-255)
    - Manufacturing department, 1942 (Box 7:, Folder 256-258)
    - Machine shop, 1941 (Box 7:, Folder 259)
    - Norris and Elliott - labor incentive plan, 1944 (Box 7:, Folder 260-261)
    - Nuclear engineering, 1952 (Box 7:, Folder 262)
    - Randupson process report, 1940 (Box 7:, Folder 263)
    - Recruitment of machinist in the U.K., 1967 (Box 7:, Folder 264)
    - Roll department, 1943 (Box 7:, Folder 265)
    - Scovell, Wellington and Co., 1934-1935 (Box 7:, Folder 266-270)
    - Sherman Anti Trust Act and USM, 1972 (Box 7:, Folder 271)
    - Systems survey for mechanization, 1955 (Box 7:, Folder 272)
  - Subseries H: Subject Files
    - Advisory Board, 1972 (Box 7:, Folder 273)
    - Akron plant, 1944 (Box 7:, Folder 274-277)
    - Atwood division, 1945-1946 (Box 8:, Folder 278-280)
    - Banbury mixer, 1923-1936 (Box 8:, Folder 281-287)
    - Beaudry Co. agreement, 1928-1929 (Box 8:, Folder 288)
    - David Bridge and Co., Ltd., 1972-1974 (Box 8:, Folder 289)
    - Bridgeport Forge Co., 1883 (Box 8:, Folder 290)
    - Buffalo operations, 1920-1962 (Box 8:, Folder 291307)
    - Classification of sales, 1900-1905 (Box 8:, Folder 308)
    - Consolidated Machine Tool Corp. - correspondence, 1952 (Box 8:, Folder 309)
    - Consolidated Machine Tool Corp. - historical, 1965 (Box 8:, Folder 310)
    - Consolidated Machine Tool Corp. - historical, 1948 (Box 8:, Folder 311)
    - Consolidated Machine Tool Corp. - historical, 1952 (Box 8:, Folder 312)
    - Depression era, 1931-1933, 1945 (Box 8A:, Folder 313-316)
    - Emhart Corp., 1974-1981 (Box 8A:, Folder 317)
    - Flood damage, 1955, 1957 (Box 8A:, Folder 318)
    - Gearflex coupling, 1940 (Box 8A:, Folder 319)
    - Giustina Co., 1966 (Box 8A:, Folder 320)
    - Hitchcock, Carl - Japan tour, 1953 (Box 8A:, Folder 321)
    - Insurance policies, 1863-1895 (Box 8A:, Folder 322)
    - Labor strikes, 1915 (Box 8A:, Folder 323)
    - Labor strikes, 1963 (Box 8A:, Folder 324)
    - Lawsuits, 1879-1890 (Box 8A:, Folder 325)
    - Lawsuits - Hydropress, Inc., 1950-1953 (Box 8A:, Folder 326-329)
    - Licenses, 1949 (Box 9:, Folder 330)
    - Licenses, 1963 (Box 9:, Folder 331)
    - Loy and Nawrath division, 1947 (Box 9:, Folder 332)
    - Machine wages and sales classification, 1912-1935 (Box 9:, Folder 333)
    - Manning table, 1943 (Box 9:, Folder 334-339)
    - Mining activities, 1884-1890 (Box 9:, Folder 340)
    - Mining activities, 1901 (Box 9:, Folder 341)
    - Mining activities, 1910-1912 (Box 9:, Folder 342)
    - Mining activities, 1912-1913 (Box 9:, Folder 343)
    - Mining activities - blueprint, undated (Box 9:, Folder 344)
    - Mining activities - Cabana Mining Co., 1890-1903 (Box 9:, Folder 345)
    - Mining activities - Gold Hill, 1914 (Box 9:, Folder 346)
    - Mining activities - Liverpool Silver & Copper Co., 1912-1914 (Box 9:, Folder 347)
    - Mining activities - newsclippings, 1904 (Box 9:, Folder 348)
    - Mining activities - prospectus and assays, 1891 (Box 9:, Folder 349)
    - National Recovery Act, 1933 (Box 9:, Folder 350)
    - National Recovery Administration, 1933 (Box 9:, Folder 351)
    - Navy vessel production, 1951 (Box 9:, Folder 352)
    - Old Timers' Club, 1967 (Box 9:, Folder 353)
    - Old Timers' Club, 1968 (Box 9:, Folder 354)
    - Old Timers' Club - newsclippings, 1961 (Box 9:, Folder 355)
    - Old Timers' Club - publicity, 1941-1969 (Box 9:, Folder 356)
    - Old Timers' Club - publicity, 1941-1962 (Box 9:, Folder 357)
    - Press releases, 1949-1950 (1955) (Box 9:, Folder 358)
    - Production engineering - Norris and Elliott, 1940-1944 (Box 9:, Folder 359-374)
    - Proposed mergers: BIF, 1917-1927 (Box 9:, Folder 375-376)
    - Proposed mergers: BIF, 1917-1927 (Box 10:, Folder 377-378)
    - Proposed mergers: Emhart Corp., 1975 (Box 10:, Folder 379)
    - Proposed mergers: Emhart Corp. - prospectus, 1976 (Box 10:, Folder 380)
    - Proposed mergers: Emhart Corp. - study, 1975 (Box 10:, Folder 381)
    - Proposed mergers: Emhart Corp. - study, 1976 (Box 10:, Folder 382)
    - Proposed mergers: Hayes Mfg. Corp., 1944 (Box 10:, Folder 383-385)
    - Proposed mergers: USM Corporation, 1972 (Box 10:, Folder 386)
    - Proposed mergers: United Engineering and Foundry Co., 1948 (Box 10:, Folder 387)
    - Proposed plant: Derby, 1952 (Box 10:, Folder 388)
    - Rubber calendars, 1944-1945 (Box 10:, Folder 389)
    - Salary adjustment, 1943-1945 (Box 10:, Folder 390)
    - Salary adjustment - applications, 1943-1945 (Box 10:, Folder 391)
    - Salary adjustment - applications, 1943-1945 (Box 10:, Folder 392)
    - Salary adjustment - applications, 1943-1945 (Box 10:, Folder 393)
    - Salary adjustment - applications, 1943-1945 (Box 10:, Folder 394)
    - Salary adjustment - correspondence, 1943 (Box 10:, Folder 395)
    - Salary adjustment - correspondence, 1944 (Box 10:, Folder 396)
    - Salary adjustment - correspondence, 1944 (Box 10:, Folder 397)
    - Salary adjustment - correspondence, 1944 (Box 10:, Folder 398)
    - Salary adjustment - correspondence, 1945 (Box 10:, Folder 399)
    - Salary adjustment - correspondence, 1945 (Box 10:, Folder 400)
    - Salary adjustment - correspondence, 1945 (Box 10:, Folder 401)
    - Salary adjustment - correspondence, 1945 (Box 10:, Folder 402)
    - Salary adjustment - requests, 1943-1945 (Box 10:, Folder 403)
    - Scientific management study, 1911-1913 (Box 10:, Folder 404-406)
    - Statistics of manufacturers, 1890 (Box 10:, Folder 407)
    - Sugar mills, 1873-1967 (Box 10:, Folder 408-410)
    - Tests, 1976 (Box 10:, Folder 411)
    - Trademarks: Watson Stillman Co., 1958 (Box 10:, Folder 412)
    - USM Corp., 1969-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 413)
    - USM Corp. - merger, 1968-1969 (Box 10:, Folder 414)
    - USM Corp. - merger, 1968-1969 (Box 10:, Folder 415)
    - USM Corp. - organizational chart, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 416)
    - USM Corp. - organizational chart, 1977 (Box 10:, Folder 417)
    - USM Corp. - prospectus, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 418)
    - USM Corp. - publications, 1968-1972 (Box 10:, Folder 419)
    - USM Corp. - stock records, 1968-1971 (Box 10:, Folder 420)
    - USM Corp. - stock records, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 421)
    - Waterbury Farrel Co., 1953-1957 (Box 10:, Folder 422-424)
    - Watson Stillman Co., 1966 (Box 11:, Folder 425)
    - World War II
      - Awards “E”, 1943-1945 (Box 11:, Folder 426-430)
      - Awards “M”, 1944 (Box 11:, Folder 431-435)
      - Contract negotiations, 1942-1945 (Box 11:, Folder 436-437)
      - History, 1941-1945 (Box 11:, Folder 438)
      - Merchant marine, 1942-1946 (Box 11:, Folder 439)
      - Military tire program, 1945 (Box 11:, Folder 440)
      - Navy filing system, 1941 (Box 11:, Folder 441)
      - Salary adjustment (Box 11:, Folder 442-443)
      - Salary stabilization appeal (Box 11:, Folder 444-447)
      - Selective service replacement, 1944-1945 (Box 11:, Folder 448-451)
      - VE, VJ Day, 1944-1945 (Box 11:, Folder 452)
    - Young and Farrel Diamond Stone Sawing Co., 1896-1900 (Box 11:, Folder 453-457)
  - Subseries I: Stock Records
    - Certificate of income of capital stock, 1871 (Box 11:, Folder 458)
    - Certificate of increased stock, 1852-1855 (Box 11:, Folder 459)
    - Certificate of payment of stock, 1864 (Box 11:, Folder 460)
    - Dividend accounts, 1931-1945 (Box 11:, Folder 461-472)
    - Dividend accounts, 1931-1945 (Box 12:, Folder 473-475)
    - Dividend accounts, 1927 (Box 12:, Folder 476)
    - Dividend record, 1859-1909 (Box 12:, Folder 477)
    - Dividend sheets, 1851-1852 (Box 12:, Folder 478)
    - F-B Internationale, 1956-1960 (Box 12:, Folder 479-480)
    - Issuance of stock, 1920 (Box 12:, Folder 481)
    - Meetings of the voting trustees, 1945-1968 (Box 12:, Folder 482-484)
    - Proxy votes, 1867-1869 (Box 12:, Folder 485)
    - Stockholders' meeting, 1968 (Box 12:, Folder 486)
    - Stockholders' of record, 1856 (Box 12:, Folder 487)
    - Subordinated notes, 1936 (Box 12:, Folder 488-489)
    - Transfer of stock, 1854 (Box 12:, Folder 490)
    - Transfer of stock, 1857-1860 (Box 12:, Folder 491)
    - Transfer of stock, 1857-1860 (Box 12:, Folder 492)
    - Transfer of stock, 1857-1860 (Box 12:, Folder 493)
    - Transfer of stock, 1857-1860 (Box 12:, Folder 494)
    - Transfer of stock, 1857-1860 (Box 12:, Folder 495)
    - Transfer of stock, 1857-1894 (Box 12:, Folder 496)
    - Transfer of stock, 1865-1866 (Box 12:, Folder 497)
    - Transfer of stock, 1874 (Box 12:, Folder 498)
- Series II: Correspondence, 1845-1966
  - Subseries A: General
    - [1840s] (Box 13:, Folder 499)
    - 1845 January - 1923 December (Box 13:, Folder 500-574)
    - 1924 January (Box 14:, Folder 575)
    - 1966 July (Box 14:, Folder 576-600)
    - 1935 December - 1936 August (Box 14:, Folder 601)
    - 1946 May - 1956 December (Box 14:, Folder 602)
    - 1959 July (Box 14:, Folder 603)
    - 1966 July (Box 14:, Folder 604)
  - Subseries B: Letter press copy books
    - Franklin Farrel, 1878 February - 1891 August (Box 14:, Folder 605)
    - Franklin Farrel, 1892 March - 1893 November (Box 14:, Folder 606)
    - Franklin Farrel, 1894 January - 1895 June (Box 14:, Folder 607)
    - Franklin Farrel, 1895 December - 1897 October (Box 14:, Folder 608)
    - Farrel Foundry and Machine Co., 1890 May - 1890 June (Box 15:, Folder 609)
    - Farrel Foundry and Machine Co., 1893 December - 1895 December (Box 15:, Folder 610)
    - S.L. Marsden, 1879 July - 1883 March (Box 15:, Folder 611)
  - Subseries C: Convertible Notes, 1938-1944
    - Convertible Notes, 1938 (Box 15:, Folder 612)
    - Convertible Notes, 1938 (Box 15:, Folder 613)
    - Convertible Notes, 1938 (Box 15:, Folder 614)
    - Convertible Notes, 1939 (Box 15:, Folder 615)
    - Convertible Notes, 1940 (Box 15:, Folder 616)
    - Convertible Notes, 1941 (Box 15:, Folder 617)
    - Convertible Notes, 1942 (Box 15:, Folder 618)
    - Convertible Notes, 1943 (Box 15:, Folder 619)
    - Convertible Notes, 1943 (Box 15:, Folder 620)
    - Convertible Notes, 1944 (Box 15:, Folder 621)
- Series III: Sales and Marketing, 1864-1956
  - Scrapbooks
    - Ansonia
      - General, 1941-1944 (Box 16:, Folder 622)
      - General, 1948-1953 (Box 16:, Folder 623)
      - General, 1953-1955 (Box 16:, Folder 624)
      - Ansonia News, 1939-1940 (Box 16:, Folder 625)
      - Ansonia News, 1956 (Box 16:, Folder 626)
    - Buffalo
      - General, 1937-1950 (Box 17:, Folder 627)
      - Marine, 1937-1943 (Box 17:, Folder 628)
      - Marine, 1943-1952 (Box 17:, Folder 629)
      - Marine, 1952 (Box 17:, Folder 630)
      - Industrial, 1944-1946 (Box 17:, Folder 631)
      - Industrial, 1946-1949 (Box 18:, Folder 632)
      - Industrial, 1949-1951 (Box 18:, Folder 633)
      - Industrial, 1951-1953 (Box 18:, Folder 634)
      - Industrial, 1953-1956 (Box 18:, Folder 635)
      - Industrial, 1956 (Box 18:, Folder 636)
    - Metal and plastic
      - Iron Age, 1928-1930 (Box 19:, Folder 637)
      - Metal working, 1929-1936 (Box 19:, Folder 638)
      - Metal working, 1937 (Box 19:, Folder 639)
      - Metal working, 1945-1951 (Box 19:, Folder 640)
      - Metal working, 1951-1955 (Box 19:, Folder 641)
      - Metal working, 1955 (Box 19:, Folder 642)
      - Metal working and plastic, 1924-1929 (Box 20:, Folder 643)
      - Metal working and plastic, 1929-1930 (Box 20:, Folder 644)
    - Paper
      - General, 1924-1926 (Box 20:, Folder 645)
      - General, 1927-1933 (Box 20:, Folder 646)
      - General, 1933-1936 (Box 20:, Folder 647)
      - General, 1937-1948 (Box 21:, Folder 648)
      - General, 1949-1953 (Box 21:, Folder 649)
      - General, 1954 (Box 21:, Folder 650)
      - Wood Pulp News, 1927-1932 (Box 21:, Folder 651)
    - Rubber
      - India Rubber Review, 1924-1935 (Box 21:, Folder 652)
      - India Rubber World, 1924-1937 (Box 21:, Folder 653)
      - India Rubber World, 1928-1929 (Box 22:, Folder 654)
      - Rubber, 1928-1930 (Box 22:, Folder 655)
      - Rubber and plastics, 1937-1946 (Box 22:, Folder 656)
      - Rubber and plastics, 1946-1949 (Box 22:, Folder 657)
      - Rubber and plastics, 1949-1952 (Box 22:, Folder 658)
      - Rubber and plastics, 1952-1955 (Box 23:, Folder 659)
      - Rubber and plastics, 1955 (Box 23:, Folder 660)
    - Sugar
      - Facts about Sugar, 1925-1927 (Box 23:, Folder 661)
      - Facts about Sugar, 1927-1936 (Box 23:, Folder 662)
      - International Sugar Journal, 1924-1936 (Box 23:, Folder 663)
      - L.A. Industrial Sugar News, 1926-1933 (Box 24:, Folder 664)
      - El Mundo, 1924-1932 (Box 24:, Folder 665)
      - Planter and sugar manufacture, 1924-1929 (Box 24:, Folder 666)
      - Sugar, 1924-1929 (Box 24:, Folder 667)
      - Sugar, 1924-1927 (Box 24:, Folder 668)
      - Sugar, 1937-1951 (Box 25:, Folder 669)
      - Sugar, 1951 (Box 25:, Folder 670)
    - General subject
      - Company matters, 1901-1917 (Box 25:, Folder 671)
      - Company products, 1908-1910 (Box 25:, Folder 672)
      - Company products, 1909 (Box 25:, Folder 673)
      - Company products, 1922 (Box 25:, Folder 674)
      - Diesel Times, 1945-1950 (Box 26:, Folder 675)
      - Directory ads, 1948 (Box 26:, Folder 676)
      - Directory ads, 1935-1948 (Box 26:, Folder 677)
      - General, 1926-1931 (Box 26:, Folder 678)
      - General, 1933-1935 (Box 26:, Folder 679)
      - General, 1944-1948 (Box 27:, Folder 680)
      - General Fortune (mech. Eng.), 1944-1956 (Box 27:, Folder 681)
      - Grain rolls, 1931 (Box 27:, Folder 682)
    - Catalogs
      - Atwood Machine Co. (Box 28:, Folder 683)
      - Buffalo division (Box 28:, Folder 684)
      - Bulletin 1400C (Box 28:, Folder 685)
      - Bulletins 102, 153-156 (Box 28:, Folder 686)
      - Bulletins 157-162, 181 (Box 28:, Folder 687)
      - Bulletins 250-253 (Box 28:, Folder 688)
      - Consolidated Machine Tool Division (Box 28:, Folder 689)
      - Farrel and Bacon crushing machinery, 1920 (Box 28:, Folder 690)
      - Farrel and Marsden stone crushers (Box 28:, Folder 691)
      - F-B, Ansonia division, vol. 1 (Box 28:, Folder 692-696)
      - F-B, Ansonia division, vol. 11 (Box 28:, Folder 697-701)
      - F-B, Buffalo division (Box 28:, Folder 702-705)
      - F-B machinery (Box 28:, Folder 706)
      - Gear machinery (Box 28:, Folder 707-708)
      - Plants and products, 1949 (Box 28:, Folder 709)
      - Rolling mill machinery (Box 28:, Folder 710)
      - Rolling mill machinery - parts (Box 28:, Folder 711-712)
      - Rubber machinery (Box 28:, Folder 3)
      - Sugar machinery (Box 28:, Folder 714)
      - Watson Stillman Co. (Box 28:, Folder 715)
      - Wheel and pulley patterns, 1865 (Box 28:, Folder 716)
    - Sales
      - Advertisements, 1885-1968 (Box 28:, Folder 717)
      - Foundry book [orders], 1864-1865 (Box 28:, Folder 718)
      - List of orders, 1882-1889 (Box 28:, Folder 719)
      - List of orders - Buffalo, 1913 July - 1920 December (Box 28:, Folder 720-723)
      - List of orders - Buffalo, 1920 December - 1923 May (Box 28:, Folder 724)
      - Machine department sales, 1927-1928 (Box 28:, Folder 725)
      - Machine department sales, 1927-1928 (Box 28:, Folder 726)
      - Monthly sales - machine shop, 1907-1908 (Box 29:, Folder 727)
      - Order book - drawing room, 1869-1875 (Box 29:, Folder 728)
      - Order book - drawing room, 1875-1886 (Box 29:, Folder 729)
      - Order book, 1893-1903 (Box 29:, Folder 730)
      - Sales and price record, 1909 June - 1915 December (Box 29:, Folder 731)
      - Sales and price record, 1916 January - 1921 December (Box 29:, Folder 732)
      - Sales and price record, 1922 January - 1928 January (Box 29:, Folder 733)
      - Salesman's notebooks, 1910-1915 (Box 29:, Folder 734)
      - Salesman's notebooks, 1911-1914 (Box 29:, Folder 735)
      - Index to order book, no. 1, 1896 (Box 29:, Folder 736)
      - Index to orders, 1897-1900 (Box 29:, Folder 737)
      - Index or order book, no. 3, 1900-1903 (Box 29:, Folder 738)
      - Office order book #2, 1892-1893; (1 volume) (Box 29A:, Folder 739)
      - Office order book #7, 1898-1899; (1 volume) (Box 29A:, Folder 740)
- Series IV: General Accounts, 1845-1981
  - Accounts received and paid, 1927 June - 1928 July (Box 30:, Folder 741)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1928 August - 1929 October (Box 30:, Folder 742)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1929 October - 1931 February (Box 30:, Folder 743)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1931 March - 1932 January (Box 30:, Folder 744)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1932 June - 1933 November (Box 30:, Folder 745)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1935 April - 1928 July (Box 30:, Folder 746)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1936 June - 1928 July (Box 30:, Folder 747)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1936 July - 1937 July (Box 30:, Folder 748)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1937 August - 1939 December (Box 31:, Folder 749)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1940 January - 1942 March (Box 31:, Folder 750)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1942 April - 1944 February (Box 31:, Folder 751)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1944 February - 1945 August (Box 31:, Folder 752)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1945 August - 1947 March (Box 31:, Folder 753)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1947 March - 1948 October (Box 32:, Folder 754)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1948 October - 1950 June (Box 32:, Folder 755)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1950 July - 1951 December (Box 32:, Folder 756)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1952 January - 1953 May (Box 32:, Folder 757)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1953 June - 1954 September (Box 32:, Folder 758)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1954 October - 1956 January (Box 33:, Folder 759)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1956 January - 1957 June (Box 33:, Folder 760)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1957 July - 1959 July (Box 33:, Folder 761)
  - Accounts received and paid, 1959 August - 1961 October (Box 33:, Folder 762)
  - Merchandise Accounts, 1936-1939 (Box 33:, Folder 763)
  - Cash books, 1942-1943 (Box 34:, Folder 764)
  - Cash receipts and disbursements, 1976 January - 1976 December (Box 34:, Folder 765)